<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Crests>
  <Crest>
    <ID>command</ID>
    <Name>Command</Name>
    <Description>When given a command, she will obey it without questioning it. (Unlocks all commands when talking and makes them always succeed)</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>libido</ID>
    <Name>Libido</Name>
    <Description>Libido is increased to such a high level that she will never be satisfied. She will frequently masturbate and never pass up a chance to have sex.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>mindmelt</ID>
    <Name>Mindmelt</Name>
    <Description>Every time she orgasms, one memory will be erased. Consecutive orgasms will erase more important memories.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>vibrancy</ID>
    <Name>Vibrancy</Name>
    <Description>The lewder she gets, the more her body will change to match her perversion. This will give her bigger breasts, butt, and thighs.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>lactation</ID>
    <Name>Lactation</Name>
    <Description>Her breasts grow in size and she starts producing milk. The more she is milked, the more pleasure she feels.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>liberated</ID>
    <Name>Liberated</Name>
    <Description>This character will find it impossible to wear underwear. The fear of being seen is overpowered by strong desire for public masturbation and sex.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>restore</ID>
    <Name>Restore</Name>
    <Description>If deflowered, at midnight her hymen will be restored and she will forget about losing her virginity.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>siphoning</ID>
    <Name>Siphoning</Name>
    <Description>When a man orgasms while inside her, he will feel a boost in strength, while she will become tired. (Increases stats, cumulative)</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>gullible</ID>
    <Name>Gullible</Name>
    <Description>If a man says something, she believes it. The more drastic her views have been changed by this, the more trusting she becomes.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>soulchained</ID>
    <Name>Soulchained</Name>
    <Description>lf a man kisses her, she won't be able to sleep until he either cums inside of her, or tells her to leave. After three nights, the effect also ends.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>broodmother</ID>
    <Name>Broodmother</Name>
    <Description>Makes her always able to become pregnant and greatly improves fertility. Pregnancies progress at a much faster rate. The brood must grow.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>animalistic</ID>
    <Name>Animalistic</Name>
    <Description>When she becomes aroused, she will start making sounds like the animal she identifies the most as.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>breedgasm</ID>
    <Name>Breedgasm</Name>
    <Description>When a man unloads inside of her, she will become pseudo-pregnant. After two hours her stomach will reach the maximum size and she will start lactating. Wears off at midnight. Warning: Stops pregnancy!</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>cumdiction</ID>
    <Name>Cumdiction</Name>
    <Description>The next time she tastes a man's cum, she will become addicted. Heavy withdrawals if she's gone more than 24 hours without consuming semen.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>deepfocus</ID>
    <Name>Deep focus</Name>
    <Description>She feels everything that happens inside her genitals, from the labia to her ovaries. When a man's semen is inside of her, she can visualize it in her mind.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>destruction</ID>
    <Name>Destruction</Name>
    <Description>No description yet.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>forlorn</ID>
    <Name>Forlorn</Name>
    <Description>Feeling lost, alone, and powerless becomes the strongest aphrodisiac imaginable. Strong affection towards any sort of bondage.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>reduction</ID>
    <Name>Reduction</Name>
    <Description>Her presence in the physical world is reduced. A crest often used by thieves and other back alley professions.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>glow</ID>
    <Name>Glow</Name>
    <Description>Her mark will glow and be visible through 20 cm of fabric, or 3 cm of harder surfaces making it impossible to hide.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>regrowth</ID>
    <Name>Regrowth</Name>
    <Description>Her hymen regrows within an hour after having sex.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>mantraction</ID>
    <Name>Mantraction</Name>
    <Description>When there's a man nearby, she will feel discomfort if she's not within half a meter of him.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>messaging</ID>
    <Name>Messaging</Name>
    <Description>Lewd thoughts will be projected onto her very skin, turning her body into a billboard trying to get fucked.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>pheromone</ID>
    <Name>Pheromone</Name>
    <Description>Any man within 30 meters will become aroused and attracted to her. The closer he is, the stronger it gets.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>receptacle</ID>
    <Name>Receptacle</Name>
    <Description>Becomes fatigued and weak unless there's a relatively fresh deposit of semen inside of her.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>reprogram</ID>
    <Name>Reprogram</Name>
    <Description>When men tell her to change, she will, overnight. Temporary effects.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>sensitivity</ID>
    <Name>Sensitivity</Name>
    <Description>Her erogenous zones are three times more sensitive.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>slave</ID>
    <Name>Slave</Name>
    <Description>Discomfort and pain when disobeying a man.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>statistics</ID>
    <Name>Statistics</Name>
    <Description>Written on her body, the stats of how many times she have orgasmed and had sex.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>suffer</ID>
    <Name>Suffer</Name>
    <Description>Pain becomes pleasure. Rough sex feels twice as good and quickly makes her cum.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>task</ID>
    <Name>Task</Name>
    <Description>She has to finish a task within 24 hours, and she's not allowed to return home, or sleep, until she's completed said task.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>triggered</ID>
    <Name>Triggered</Name>
    <Description>Every time someone talks with her about sex, she becomes unbearably horny.</Description>
  </Crest>
  <Crest>
    <ID>violove</ID>
    <Name>Violove</Name>
    <Description>Rough play turns her on and develops affection towards the man. Does not negate or translate pain.</Description>
  </Crest>
</Crests>